Doble, William J. Papers 5182
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Big Four Signal Forces/Danville, Illinois, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 114)
- Kent Interlocking at Marion, Indiana, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 115)
- Michigan Interlocking at Elkhart-Jackson Subdivision, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  Diagram
- Flashers at Meridian St./Ohio Division, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 117)
- Armitage, Ohio, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 118)
- D.T.&I./ Adrian, Michigan, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 119)
- Dunkirk Interlocking at Dunkirk, Ohio, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 120)
- Grayville, Illinois Interlocking, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 121)
- Pana, Illinois - Signals, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 122)
- Oldsmobile Co./Cowle St., Lansing, Michigan, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 123)
- Tates Point, Ohio, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- Dean Interlocking, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 125)
- Legislative Cases in Ohio, 1952-1954 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Public Utilites Commission
- Motor Car Rules, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Motor Car Rules, 1939-1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Use of Snow Flangers, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Elimination of Motor Car Set-Offs, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Motor Car Repair, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Complaints, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  Dispatcher/Operators
- Motor Car, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  Protection for Operation of
- Motor Car "Tops", 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Article: "Safe Track Ahead", 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Accidents Involving Motor Cars, 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Complaint, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  New York Central System
- Accident, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Accident, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Case, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  Accident
- Accident Investigation, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  June 8th
- Case of N.J. Burke, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Compensation Case, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  G.F. Neil
- Minutes of Investigation, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Settlement, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Appeals for New Investigation, 1944-1949 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Investigation, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  and Minutes
- Accident Report and Ensuing Correspondence, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Collisions and Accident Convictions, 1953-1954 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Sick Leave, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Leave of Absence, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Indiana Harbor Belt Railroad, 1954-1959 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  Agreements and Correspondence
- Belt Railway Company, Agreements and Correspondence, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Maintenance Facilities (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Signal Work, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Dolton Interlocking, 1952-1955 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Ash Street Signal Work: Agreement, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Interlocking B&OCT/I.H.B. Diagrams & Correspondence, 1950-1952 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Chicago Belt Railway, 1951-1954 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Labor-Management Reports, including correspondence, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- General System Committee Minutes, 1930-1963 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  lacks, 1931, 36, 38, 39, 41-43, 48, 61-62
- By-laws; Revised, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Affiliation of "Big 4" Signalmen Locals, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- By-Laws amended, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- General System Committee Reports (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Semi-Annual Report of Secretary-Treasurer, 1930-1962 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Financial Statements of General Systems Committee, 1933-1951 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Grand Lodge Semi-Monthly Expense Report, 1958-1963 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Expense Account - R.L. Giant (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Meeting of General Chairmen - Minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  Association of General Chairman
- Demotion of J.M. Pattee (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Agenda Committee (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Addresses and Correspondence, 1939-1962 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Election of Vice Chairman, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- War Time (Box 2, Folder 50)
- I.R.S. Statements, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Federal Income Tax, 1927-1956 (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Reports of General Chairmen (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Personal Letters (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Leave of Absence Forms (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Tax Returns, 1936-1937 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  quarterly
- U.S. Railroad Retirement Beard, 1935-1951 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  Receipts, Certificate of Service
- I.R.S./Railroad Retirement Board, 1937-1944 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  .
- By-laws (Box 2, Folder 59)
- By-laws (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Social Security Act, 1936 (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Benefits for Railroad Employees - pamphlets (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Diagrams of Provisions for Employees (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Agreements and Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Case of Race Motor Sales (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Shoemaker, Drum, Halbut (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Ragsdale (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Lines West (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Lines East (Box 3, Folder 5)
- General Correspondence, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Rate Adjustment, 1952-1954 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Signalman's Relief Fund, 1931-1932 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Union Pacific Railroad (Box 3, Folder 9)
- South Pacific Railroad vs. Brotherhood of Railroad Signalman, 1930 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Railway Labor Act, 1926-1929 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Aurand (Box 3, Folder 12)
  direct correspondence
- Weigand (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Correspondence between Aurand and Pattee (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Forty Hour Work Week Agreement, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Political League, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Multiple Copies of Agreement (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Revised Agreement (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Car Retarder Technicians, 1957-1960 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Pittsburgh Lake Erie Railroad Agreement, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Changes in District 2 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Quarterly Financial Statements, 1934-1941 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Quarterly Financial Statements, 1949-1962 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Northern District, 1958-1962 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Canada Division, 1951-1962 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Erie Signal District, 1954-1962 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Cleveland Signal District, 1954-1962 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Toledo Signal District, 1954-1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Western Signal District, 1956-1962 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Chicago Terminal Signal District, 1954-1962 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Southern District, 1954-1961 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Cleveland Union Terminal, 1954-1960 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Indiana Harbor Belt Railway District, 1949-1961 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Elkhart Signal Shop, 1949-1962 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Ohio Central District, 1953-1962 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Indiana Division, 1954-1962 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Illinois Division, 1954-1962 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Pittsburgh Lake Erie Railroad Co., 1951-1959 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Western District No. 2 - Inspector-Foreman, 1953-1961 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Southern District No. 3 - Foremen, Inspectors, 1953-1961 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Northern District No. 4 -, 1956-1963 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Northern District No. 5, 1956-1961 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Retarder Technicians, District No. 7, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Report of General Officers, 1936-1938 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  11/1/36-10/31/38
- Officer's Reports and Minutes, Convention, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  August
- 1938 Controversy and Settlement (Box 4, Folder 26)
  March
- Pamphlets on Railroad Wages (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Wage Reduction Proposal, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Wage Reduction Proposal, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- 1931 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Wage Increase of 1929 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Agreement, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  April 1st
- Wage Increase, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Wage Increase, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Wage Increase Request, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Wage Increase Request, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Request for Increase, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- National Wage Actions, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- List of Rates, 1947-1956 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  US & Canada
- Wage Increase, 1955 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- 1956 Wage Movement (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Vacations/Seniority Rights, 1942-1946 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Re-employment Rights, 1940-1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Merchant Marines, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Employment Policy, 1941-1945 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Selective Training and Service Act, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- On the Job Training (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Re-Inlistment, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Promotions, 1946-1950 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Vacation Cases, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Education Benefits, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Education Benefits - Leaves of Absence, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Seniority /Enlistment, 1944-1946 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Bureau of Veterans Re-employment Rights - Field Letters, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Re-employment Rights Continued by Extension of Social Security Act, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Reinstatement Rights, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Leave of Absence for Enlistment, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Vacated Positions, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Public Law 51 - Employees in Military Service, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Public Laws - Vocational Rehabilitation Publications (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Veteran's Readjustment Act, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Displacement Rights, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Agreement, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  12/20/34 revised 7/2/36
- Michigan Central, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Erie and Franklin Divisions, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Old Illinois Division, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Grand Rapids, 1934-1936 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  Unification of Terminals
- Michigan Central/NYC, 1934-1935 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Michigan Central/Seniority Rights, 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Illinois Division/Seniority Districts, 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Western Signal District-Seniority, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Agreement, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Seniority Dispute - Western Signal District/Chicago Terminal District, 1932-1935 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Consolidation of Locals 28 and 42, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Seniority Roster
- Peoria and Eastern Railroad - Indianapolis, 1934-1944 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Pamphlets concerning CTC (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Memorandum - Positions connected with CTC Erie Division, 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Extension of CTC Installations, 1955-1957 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Western District Agreement, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Installation between Elkhart, Ind./ Jackson, Michigan, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Employment under CTC/Yard Extension Program, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Differential Pay Rates, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Agreement - Seniority District - Ohio and Indiana Divisions, Change in Jurisdictions, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Position of Signal Maintainer, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Operating Practices for Gateway Yard (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Maintenance Foreman, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- New Agreement, Inspectors/Foremen, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Educational and Training Program, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- CTC "Territory", 1957 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Lunch Time, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Highway Crossing Protection, 1957-1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Assistant Training Program, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Lay-Offs/Unexcused Absence, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- "Notice" (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Section 6 -Railway Labor Act
- Dispute Railway Employees Department / New York Central Railroad, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Furloughed Employee Status, 1956-1959 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Railroad Retirement Board, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Working in the Rain, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Transfer of Signal Maintenance Sections From Western Signal District to Chicago Terminal District, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Pipe Work - Craft Jurisdiction, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Trench Work - Jurisdiction, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Seniority Status of J.C. Wyatt, 1960-1962 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Signal Shop at Elkhart, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Canada: Highway Crossing Protective Devices, 1957-1959 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Lost Time - Due to Medical Exam, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Canada Division-District 3, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Accident at Ligonie, Ind. /Dismissals, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Signalman's Agreement - Labor Relations, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Seniority Case - Elkhart, Ind., 1958-1961 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Chauffeur's Licenses - N.Y.S., 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Maintenance Coverage, Erie CTC, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Name Change From BRSof A to BRS, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Consolidation of Locals 28 and 42, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Passenger Train Service Bill, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Transfer of Local Jurisdiction, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  locals 15, 30, 41
- Signal Construction Force, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Inspection Force, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- A.J. Scheider Case, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Increase Per Capita Tax to Grand Lodge, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Membership Transfer, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  Local 76 to 210
- Status of two employees at High Bridge, N.Y., Signal Shop, 1953-1959 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Investigation of Derailment at Short Cut Interlocker, Detroit, Toledo and Ironton Railroad Co., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Repair of Electronic Equipment, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Case Wiring Work at Lyons, NY, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Hump Classification Yard at Indianapolis, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Reimbursement of Mr. Kalyncz, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Lunch Period - Cleveland Signal District, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Vacations, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  Erie Division
- Michigan Cooperative Safety Plan, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Annual Vacation Act: Canada, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Transfer of Jurisdiction over Ohio Central Division from West to South District, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  July
- System Signal Shop Roster, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  Displacement Routes at High Bridge, NY
- Representation of Signalment - Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Railroad Co., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Landrum-Griffith Act, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Ohio AFL-CIO, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Mediation Agreement, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Unexcused Absences - Elkhart Shop, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Company Policy of Father/Son Working Together, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Rearrangement in Western Operating District, 1956-1971 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Commutation Traffic Study, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  New York City
- Vacation Agreement, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Affiliation/Constitution AFL-CIO, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- State Voting Procedures, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  Time off
- Detroit Bomb Shelter Company (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Wage Agreement, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Agreement of Louisville and Nashville Railroad Co., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- Grievances (Box 6, Folder 61)
- Highway Commission, 1931-1938 (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Michigan State Projects (Box 6, Folder 63)
- Wage Compensation, 1938-1939 (Box 6, Folder 64)
- Foremen - Promotions, 1936-1942 (Box 6, Folder 65)
- ICC Employee Classification/National Mediation Board, 1941-1947 (Box 6, Folder 66)
- Case of A. A. Unmitz/W.K.Hunt, 1940-1941 (Box 6, Folder 67)
- U.S. Office of Education, 1942 (Box 6, Folder 68)
- Expense Account, 1939-1941 (Box 6, Folder 69)
- Agreement-Governing Foreman Position, 1921 (Box 6, Folder 70)
- Performing Work Belonging to Employees, 1931-1950 (Box 6, Folder 71)
- Notice of Foreman Positions, 1937-1947 (Box 6, Folder 72)
- Foremans Agreement, 1924 (Box 6, Folder 73)
- Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America Agreement, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  Representing Foremen and Inspectors in Dispute
- Promotions and Representation of Foremen by BRS of A, 1937-1951 (Box 6, Folder 75)
- Advertise Positions Temporarily Vacant, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Proposed Revision to Foremen's Agreement, 1953-1954 (Box 6, Folder 77)
- Vacation Pay, 1940-1942 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Vacations With Pay, 1940-1941 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Vacation Plan, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Vacation Plan, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Vacation Plan, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Vacation Plan, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Vacation Plan, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Vacation Plan, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Vacation Plan, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Vacation Plan, 1950-1952 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Vacation Plan, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Decisions-Vacations for Non Operating Employees, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- NRAB-Dispute Claim, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Claim of L.J. Kensler, 1947-1949 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Claim of T.A. Kilian, 1944-1945 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Claim of Hoffman and Darby, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Claim of Gordon Jones, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Claim of R.C. Hughes, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Men at the W, Hump, Detroit, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Men Entering Military Service, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Elkhart Indiana Vacation Schedule, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Memo - Toledo, OH, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Messrs. Langely and Clark, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Case of A. Lohrum, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Agreement Between Indiana Harbor Belt. Co. BRSA, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Agreement, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Consolidated Agreement, 1944-1953 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- BRSA/NYC Agreement, 1931-1940 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  Peoria and Eastern Railroad -Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago and St. Louis Railroad
- Revision of Agreement, 1935-1940 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Proposed Revisions /Negotiations, 1937-1938 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Agreement - Big Four/BRSA, 1940 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  March 5th
- Revision of Michigan Central Agreement -Negotiations, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Consolidated Agreement - Proposed Revisions, 1947-1950 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Indiana Harbor Belt Company /BRSofA, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Big Four - 1949 Supplement, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Indiana Harbor Belt Company 1949 Supplement & Revisions, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Memorandum of Agreement Pittsburgh and Lake Erie, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Supplement to Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Agreement, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Committee Decisions, 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Force Reductions, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 40)
- Cleveland Local: Schedule Dispute, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Deviation From Monday-Friday Work, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  memo
- Lousiville & Nashville/Nashville, Chattanooga & St. Louis Memo Agreement, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Pay Dispute, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Claim of H.M. Thompson concerning Pay, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Claim of G. Orndorff, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Agreement, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  March 19th
- Memo of Rule 18 Revision, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Indiana Harbor Belt Co. Agreement Revision, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Pittsburgh and Lake Erie Memo Revision, 1949 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Seniority Rights in International District, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Six Holidays, 1942 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- General Orders - Railway Commissioners of Canada, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Income Tax Deduction, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Selective Service Data (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Wage Standards, 1941-1946 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Orders in Council, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  September
- General Order, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  May
- Pamphlets/Information (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Labor-Management Relations (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Railway Labor Relations, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Personnel, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Contribution of Employees to Good Public Relations (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Definition of a Customer, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Pension Rackets (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Federal Employer's Liability Act (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Representation of Signal Draftsmen, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Installation of Nuclear Switch Lamps, 1954-1960 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- ICC - Employee Classification, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Revision of Basic Agreements, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Transfer of Maintenance Section, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Application to National Mediation Board, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Working On/Near Highway Crossings, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Recall of Furloughed Employees on Michigan Central, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Submission of Claims-Grievances, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Meeting RE: 1954 Agreement, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  March 21st
- Lakefront Dock and Railroad Terminal Co., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Leaves of Absence to Permit Employees to Engage in Outside Employment (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Indiana Gross Income Tax, 1954-1957 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Co-operating Railway Labor Organizations (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Housing Units for Signal Gongs, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Jury Duty (Absence), 1955-1961 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Canadian National Railway - Signal Maintenance, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Equipment Budget, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Position Numbers, 1955-1953 (Box 8, Folder 39)
- 10 - A or Suprise Test, 1950-1952 (Box 8, Folder 40)
- Railway Labor Act (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Railroad Transportation Act (Box 8, Folder 42)
- Association of American Railroads, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 43)
- Rules & Regulations Governing Railroad Radio Service, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 44)
- System Signal Shop, 1954-1961 (Box 8, Folder 45)
- Maintenance of Rail Head Bonds, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 46)
- Signal Department Questionnaire, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 47)
- New York Central Railroad - Personnel Information (Box 8, Folder 48)
- Detroit Terminal Railroad, 1952-1961 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- American Railway Supervisors Association, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Investigations & Hearings, 1947-1952 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Car Retarders, 1949-1953 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Overtime and Seniority, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Signal Inspection Test, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Supervisory Forces Hauling Signal Material, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Installation of Snow Melters on Erie Division, 1957-1961 (Box 8, Folder 56)
- Case of J. Pempeck, 1951-1956 (Box 8, Folder 57)
- South District-Installation and Procurement of Factory Wired Relay Cases and Housings, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 58)
- By-Laws Governing General System Committee (Box 8, Folder 59)
- State Public Service Acts Pertaining to Railroads, 1949-1957 (Box 8, Folder 60)
- Operation of Company Trucks, 1958-1961 (Box 8, Folder 61)
- Double-Time Rate After 15 Hours, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 62)
- "60 Calendar Days" Revision, 1960-1962 (Box 8, Folder 63)
- Responsibilities of Leading Signal Mechanic, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 64)
- 30 Minute Lunch Period, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Pay Claim of L.J. Miller, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 66)
- Pay for Temporary Position, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 67)
- Claim for Expenses for Meal Period Under Rule 18, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 68)
- Displacement Routes, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 69)
- Strike Settlement Claims, 1952-1954 (Box 8, Folder 70)
- Promoted Man's Position Abolished, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Promotions, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 72)
- Case of Toronto, Hamilton, and Buffalo, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 73)
- Travel Time, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 74)
- Furnish Soap for Cars, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Rates of Pay for Leading Signal Maintenances, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 76)
- Heating Facilities, 1951-1954 (Box 8, Folder 77)
- Seniority/Higher Pay Rates, 1952-1961 (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Overtime Claim of D.J. Britton, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 79)
- Application of Rule 33, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 80)
- Make-Up Time, 1958-1959 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  Rule 18
- Overtime - D.L. Shultz, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 82)
- Telephone at Company Expense, 1946-1953 (Box 8, Folder 83)
- Filing of Claims, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Plant Transportation Committee, 1942-1944 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- District Construction Gangs (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Special Board of Adjustment, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Elkhart Signal Shop Consolidation, 1954-1955 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Vacation and Holiday Rules Movement, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Health and Welfare, Life Insurance, Cost-of-Living Escalator (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Rules Movement, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Wage and Rules Movement, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Expense Sheets, 1954-1958 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Meeting of Executive Committee and Signal Engineers in Detroit, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Agreement NYC/Retarder Technicians, Inspectors Foremen Employed in Signal Department, 1958-1960 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Tax Statements, 1960-1961 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Bound Ledger of Personal Expenses, 1952-1958 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Awards Made By Special Board of Adjustment (1-5) (Box 10, Folder 2)
- CTC Project, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 3)